glamsham.com 2014-06-27

# Privacy@glamsham.com

| 

### What's Hot and Trending in Bollywood

|   
|  |  |  |   
|   

**glamsham.com's Privacy Policy.**

**At glamsham.com, we are very committed to your privacy, glamsham.com will never sell, exchange, or release any of your individual personal information to a third party without your express permission.**

 **INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT:**  
At our site, we do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not require you to register or provide information to us in order to view our site. We only gather personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by a visitor except for our Web based email services which requires a person to enter perosnal information.

From time to time, we may conduct online surveys or run a contest for promotional purposes, during which, we may ask users for contact information (like email addresses) and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data to notify people if they win the contest. We understand, though, that you may want to participate in these surveys or contests but may not want us to send you email. Accordingly, as part of these surveys or contests, we will always give you the option of declining to receive information from glamsham.com. If you don't want to receive email, just let us know, and we won't send it.

Like other web sites, your IP number is visible to us when you visit our web site. Your IP number is visible to most of the websites that you visit. Tthough, at glamsham.com, we only use IP numbers to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our Web site.

We may share personally identifiable information with third parties when the person submitting the information authorises us to share it or we are required to by law. 

**COOKIES**  
Like many sites, glamsham.com uses cookies. Cookies are data files that are stored on your computer. They contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. 

We use cookies for the benefit of our users. Cookies let us know if we have repeat visitors (a strong indication of happy consumers) and if we are delivering a quality product to our consumers. We also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites. glamsham.com does not use cookies to identify specific individuals, except in such cases as contest registration (where a cookie allows to you to enter a contest every day without registering again each time) and personalisation features where a guest requests certain information. glamsham.com never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. glamsham.com does not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes. Essentially, it is an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for other consumers who we think will like our site. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES**  
glamsham.com contains many links to other sites. glamsham.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. glamsham.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide glamsham.com with the sites to which glamsham.com links, although glamsham.com may share aggregate data with such sites (such as how many people use our site). This Includes other third party sites on the Internet for which glamsham.com provides search services. Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**  
We use MaxWorldwide, Google and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [please click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**THIRD PARTY COOKIES**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**UNSUBSCRIBE**  
**If you wish to unsubscribe, kindly Click Here**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with glamsham.com, please write to: response@glamsham.com

|  |  |   
---  
  
  * Movie Review
  * Music Review
  * Preview

**Humshakals** \- movie review  
Sajid Khan's HUMSHAKALS has kindergarten humour at its best. Riteish Deskmukh stands out with his co...  
  
**Machhli Jal Ki Rani Hai** \- movie review  
So, in a hurry to quicken the pace, the director felt it apt to push her foot on the accelerator. Wh...  

 **more...**  
  
  * Celeb Wallpapers
  * Movie Wallpapers

Kriti Sanon

Shraddha Kapoor

**more...**  
  
  * Posters
  * Stills
  * Screensavers

Humpty Sharma Ki Dulhania

Mardaani

**more...**  
  
  * Events Gallery
  * Celeb Gallery

Shahrukh Khan set to take a ride at Bandra

Amitabh Bachchan dubs at Empire studio

**more...**  
  
### Tags

Rakul Preet Singh Hard Kaur Amrita Puri Monali Thakur Mugdha Godse Aamir Khan Shilpa Shetty Manisha Kelkar Neha Sharma Dia Mirza Nushrat Bharucha Deepika Padukone Tiger Shroff Uday Chopra Sandeepa Dhar Complete List
